Backtest 0.92. Live: -40%. Why?
Sensitivity measurement —
which parameters actually move fitness?
12 axes probed. 3 carry signal. 9 are decoys.
Top-K unlock — grid only over the axes that matter.
50 combinations searched. Best train fitness: 12.00.
But does it generalise?
Walk-forward — replay best on held-out data.
Pearson 0.879.
KC-4 threshold 0.50, declared up-front.
Cannot be lowered after seeing the score.
All four kill criteria PASS.
Train-rank predicts test-rank. Ship.
Fractal vise refines further.
alpha 0.5 → 0.4375. Same discipline, finer grid.
Works for any CalibrableTarget.
Trading. Prompts. Any hyperparameter.
pip install omega-lock
Apache 2.0 · 176 tests · 0 network in CI